Office of the Provost and Senior Vice President Records UA002
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Faculty records, 1924 -- 2012; UA002.008; 19.7 Linear Feet
  - Medical School Dean Search, 1995 -- 2002; UA002.008.066.00040 (Box 66)
  - Dental Dean Search, 1994 -- 1996; UA002.008.066.00041 (Box 66)
  - Fletcher Dean Search, 1994 -- 1996; UA002.008.066.00042 (Box 66)
  - Provost and Senior Vice President Search, 2001 -- 2002; UA002.008.067.00001 (Box 67)
  - Arts & Sciences Dean Search, 2005; UA002.008.067.00002 (Box 67)
  - Molly Stutzman, 2005; UA002.008.067.00003 (Box 67)
    Hotel and Conference Room Bookings
  - Charges A&S Dean Search, 2005; UA002.008.067.00004 (Box 67)
  - Arts & Sciences Dean Search, 2005; UA002.008.067.00005 (Box 67)
  - Joshua Seftel, 1995 -- 1997; UA002.008.067.00006 (Box 67)
  - Policy on Academic Freedom, Tenure, and Retirement, 1966 -- 1986; UA002.008.067.00007 (Box 67)
  - Tallloires, 1982 -- 2005; UA002.008.067.00008 (Box 67)
  - Nutrition School, 1980 -- 1989; UA002.008.067.00009 (Box 67)
  - Confidential: Backup Documentation from the Five Year Review of Robert Sternberg, 2009; UA002.008.067.00010 (Box 67)
  - Robert S Sternberg FAB Letters: Confidential, 2009; UA002.008.067.00011 (Box 67)
    Faculty Advisory Board letters for Review
  - Faculty Advisory Board Procedures for Review of Administrators, 2008 -- 2009; UA002.008.067.00012 (Box 67)
  - Michael Rosenblatt Review, 2008; UA002.008.067.00013 (Box 67)
  - Linda Abriola Review, 2008; UA002.008.067.00014 (Box 67)
  - Annual Reports, 2002 -- 2003; UA002.008.067.00015 (Box 67)
  - Abusharaf, Rogai, UA002.008.068.00001 (Box 68)
  - Adams, Reginald, UA002.008.068.00002 (Box 68)
  - Alano, Jomarie, UA002.008.068.00003 (Box 68)
  - Albertini, David, UA002.008.068.00004 (Box 68)
  - Alexander, Joseph, UA002.008.068.00005 (Box 68)
  - Alvarez-Junco, Jose, UA002.008.068.00006 (Box 68)
  - Amar Sanchez, Ana Maria, UA002.008.068.00007 (Box 68)
  - Anderson, Molly, UA002.008.068.00008 (Box 68)
  - Aprille, June, UA002.008.068.00009 (Box 68)
  - Aqua, Edward, UA002.008.068.00010 (Box 68)
  - Atkinson, Ti-Grace, UA002.008.068.00011 (Box 68)
  - Band, Vimla, UA002.008.068.00012 (Box 68)
  - Barbeau, Elizabeth, UA002.008.068.00013 (Box 68)
  - Berenguer, Angel, UA002.008.068.00014 (Box 68)
  - Bihari, Jonathan, UA002.008.068.00015 (Box 68)
  - Blumberg, Jeffrey, UA002.008.068.00016 (Box 68)
  - Brooke, John, UA002.008.068.00017 (Box 68)
  - Brown, Larry, UA002.008.068.00018 (Box 68)
  - Brown, Philip, UA002.008.068.00019 (Box 68)
  - Brown, William, UA002.008.068.00020 (Box 68)
  - Buckholt, Michael, UA002.008.068.00021 (Box 68)
  - Cai, Cindy, UA002.008.068.00022 (Box 68)
  - Carlbom, Ingrid, UA002.008.068.00023 (Box 68)
  - Cataldo, Linda, UA002.008.068.00024 (Box 68)
  - Cataudella, John, UA002.008.068.00025 (Box 68)
  - Cave, David, UA002.008.068.00026 (Box 68)
  - Chan, Dan, UA002.008.068.00027 (Box 68)
  - Chiang (Francis), Lydia, UA002.008.068.00028 (Box 68)
  - Colati, Greg, UA002.008.068.00029 (Box 68)
  - Cruz, Gabriella, UA002.008.068.00030 (Box 68)
  - Cuttino, David, UA002.008.068.00031 (Box 68)
  - Daniels, Norman, UA002.008.068.00032 (Box 68)
  - De Bernardez, Eliana, UA002.008.068.00033 (Box 68)
  - Delacampagne, Christian, UA002.008.068.00034 (Box 68)
  - Dillon, Kristine, UA002.008.068.00035 (Box 68)
  - DiTullio, Biagio, UA002.008.068.00036 (Box 68)
  - Dolins, David, UA002.008.068.00037 (Box 68)
  - Driscoll de Alvarado, Barbara, UA002.008.068.00038 (Box 68)
  - Drongowski, Paul, UA002.008.068.00039 (Box 68)
  - Duca, Karen, UA002.008.068.00040 (Box 68)
  - Edington, William, UA002.008.068.00041 (Box 68)
  - Elder, Murray, UA002.008.068.00042 (Box 68)
  - Else, James, UA002.008.068.00043 (Box 68)
  - Fahey, Jeanne, UA002.008.068.00044 (Box 68)
  - Fister, Richard, UA002.008.068.00045 (Box 68)
  - Fleming, Maureen (Hayes), UA002.008.068.00046 (Box 68)
  - Fletcher, Madeline, UA002.008.068.00047 (Box 68)
  - Galantic, Joyce, UA002.008.068.00048 (Box 68)
  - Garcia-Godoy, Franklin, UA002.008.068.00049 (Box 68)
  - Gillerman, Dorothy, UA002.008.068.00050 (Box 68)
  - Gillan, Colin, UA002.008.068.00051 (Box 68)
  - Gomes Da Cruz, Gabriela, UA002.008.068.00052 (Box 68)
  - Goode, Robert, UA002.008.068.00053 (Box 68)
  - Grainger, Ian Jonathan, UA002.008.068.00054 (Box 68)
  - Hagopian, Frances, UA002.008.068.00055 (Box 68)
  - Hale, Audrey, UA002.008.068.00056 (Box 68)
  - Hanelin, Joseph, UA002.008.068.00057 (Box 68)
  - Hawkins, Robert, UA002.008.068.00058 (Box 68)
  - Hendricks, Ann Marie, UA002.008.068.00059 (Box 68)
  - Herron, John, UA002.008.068.00060 (Box 68)
  - Ho, Shuk-Mei, UA002.008.068.00061 (Box 68)
  - Huang, Terry T-K, UA002.008.068.00062 (Box 68)
  - Jacobs, Mary Lee, UA002.008.068.00063 (Box 68)
  - Jakowski, Richard, UA002.008.068.00064 (Box 68)
  - Jansen, Daniel, UA002.008.068.00065 (Box 68)
  - Jenke, John, UA002.008.068.00066 (Box 68)
  - Johansen, Erling, UA002.008.068.00067 (Box 68)
  - Johnson, Idella, UA002.008.068.00068 (Box 68)
  - Kao, Ming, UA002.008.068.00069 (Box 68)
  - Kepler, Patricia, UA002.008.068.00070 (Box 68)
  - Kiely, Sally, UA002.008.068.00071 (Box 68)
  - King, Sarah, UA002.008.068.00072 (Box 68)
  - Lifschitz, Lucy, UA002.008.068.00073 (Box 68)
  - Ladd, Larry, UA002.008.068.00074 (Box 68)
  - Lazinski, David, UA002.008.068.00075 (Box 68)
  - Madoff, Morton, UA002.008.068.00076 (Box 68)
  - Magness, Jodi, UA002.008.068.00077 (Box 68)
  - Mandell, Robert, UA002.008.068.00078 (Box 68)
  - Mann, Samuel, UA002.008.068.00079 (Box 68)
  - Margheritis, Ana, UA002.008.068.00080 (Box 68)
  - Marshall Faux, Cynthia, UA002.008.068.00081 (Box 68)
  - Mazza, Carol, UA002.008.068.00082 (Box 68)
  - McElveen, Georgiary, UA002.008.068.00083 (Box 68)
  - McKnight, Lee, UA002.008.068.00084 (Box 68)
  - McOrist, Steven, UA002.008.068.00085 (Box 68)
  - Medina, Nadia, UA002.008.068.00086 (Box 68)
  - Mejias, Judith, UA002.008.068.00087 (Box 68)
  - Meller, Victoria, UA002.008.068.00088 (Box 68)
  - Policy on Academic Freedom, Tenure, and Retirement, 1964 -- 1971; UA002.008.069.00001 (Box 69)
  - Basic Sciences Tenure Chart, 1976 -- 2001; UA002.008.069.00002 (Box 69)
  - Faculty appotinments, tenure, and promotion in the School of Vetinary Medicine, 1988-1996, UA002.008.069.00003 (Box 69)
  - Report from the Provost to TAAC, 1983; UA002.008.069.00004 (Box 69)
  - Scientific packet from Peggy Newell, Kelly Laughlin, Dept of Biology, 2009; UA002.008.069.00005 (Box 69)
  - Degrees voted, 2003 -- 2004; UA002.008.069.00006 (Box 69)
  - Degrees voted, 2004; UA002.008.069.00007 (Box 69)
  - Degrees voted, 2004; UA002.008.069.00008 (Box 69)
  - Degrees voted, 2003; UA002.008.069.00009 (Box 69)
  - Degrees voted, 2003; UA002.008.069.00010 (Box 69)
  - Trustee notes on degrees, 1966 -- 1998; UA002.008.069.00011 (Box 69)
  - Degrees, 2002 -- 2003; UA002.008.069.00012 (Box 69)
  - Degrees, 2001 -- 2002; UA002.008.069.00013 (Box 69)
  - Mendelson, Sarah, UA002.008.069.00014 (Box 69)
  - Metz, Bruce, UA002.008.069.00015 (Box 69)
  - Moreno, Rocha, UA002.008.069.00016 (Box 69)
  - Morrison, Steven, UA002.008.069.00017 (Box 69)
  - Morsy, Soheir, UA002.008.069.00018 (Box 69)
  - Morteau, Oliver, UA002.008.069.00019 (Box 69)
  - Moss, Larry, UA002.008.069.00020 (Box 69)
  - Murnane, Dr. Thomas W., UA002.008.069.00021 (Box 69)
  - Murtaugh, Robert, UA002.008.069.00022 (Box 69)
  - Neff, Teresa, UA002.008.069.00023 (Box 69)
  - Nelson, Steven, UA002.008.069.00024 (Box 69)
  - Neuman, W. Russell, UA002.008.069.00025 (Box 69)
  - Nitsche, Monika, UA002.008.069.00026 (Box 69)
  - Oates, M. Elizabeth, UA002.008.069.00027 (Box 69)
  - O'Connell, Brian, UA002.008.069.00028 (Box 69)
  - Overstrom, Eric, UA002.008.069.00029 (Box 69)
  - Patronek, Gary, UA002.008.069.00030 (Box 69)
  - Pereira, Anthony, UA002.008.069.00031 (Box 69)
  - Posada, Viena, UA002.008.069.00032 (Box 69)
  - Postlethwaite, Bonnie, UA002.008.069.00033 (Box 69)
  - Powell, Michael, UA002.008.069.00034 (Box 69)
  - Prevelakis, George, UA002.008.069.00035 (Box 69)
  - Puliafito, Carmen, UA002.008.069.00036 (Box 69)
  - Rachele, Lizabeth, UA002.008.069.00037 (Box 69)
  - Reilly, Maura, UA002.008.069.00038 (Box 69)
  - Rich, Stephen, UA002.008.069.00039 (Box 69)
  - Rolland, Rosalind, UA002.008.069.00040 (Box 69)
  - Rusanescu, Gabriel, UA002.008.069.00041 (Box 69)
  - Ruslander, David, UA002.008.069.00042 (Box 69)
  - Rutinsky, Laura, UA002.008.069.00043 (Box 69)
  - Ryan, Kate, UA002.008.069.00044 (Box 69)
  - Sanchez, Ana Maria Amar, UA002.008.069.00045 (Box 69)
  - Schiff, Harold, UA002.008.069.00046 (Box 69)
  - Schwartzman, Harry, UA002.008.069.00047 (Box 69)
  - Schweiker, Robert, UA002.008.069.00048 (Box 69)
  - Sestak, Karol, UA002.008.069.00049 (Box 69)
  - Sharkey, Leslie, UA002.008.069.00050 (Box 69)
  - Skar, Lowell, UA002.008.069.00051 (Box 69)
  - Socrate, Simona, UA002.008.069.00052 (Box 69)
  - Solomon, Julie, UA002.008.069.00053 (Box 69)
  - Soraci, Salvatore, UA002.008.069.00054 (Box 69)
  - Stem, Edgar, UA002.008.069.00055 (Box 69)
  - Sturr, Christopher, UA002.008.069.00056 (Box 69)
  - Sylvinia, Teresa, UA002.008.069.00057 (Box 69)
  - Taylor, Jaqueline, UA002.008.069.00058 (Box 69)
  - Theodos, Cynthia, UA002.008.069.00059 (Box 69)
  - Thueson, Peter, UA002.008.069.00060 (Box 69)
  - Theon, Alain, UA002.008.069.00061 (Box 69)
  - Tokoz-Exley, Deniz, UA002.008.069.00062 (Box 69)
  - Toole, Bryan, UA002.008.069.00063 (Box 69)
  - Vaaler, Paul, UA002.008.069.00064 (Box 69)
  - Valluzzi, Regina, UA002.008.069.00065 (Box 69)
  - Vandat, Farzin, UA002.008.069.00066 (Box 69)
  - Veremis, Thanos, UA002.008.069.00067 (Box 69)
  - Wada-Marciano, Mitsuyo, UA002.008.069.00068 (Box 69)
  - Wahyudi, Yudian, UA002.008.069.00069 (Box 69)
  - Walbridge, John, UA002.008.069.00070 (Box 69)
  - Wender, Melissa, UA002.008.069.00071 (Box 69)
  - Wolf, Gerald, UA002.008.069.00072 (Box 69)
  - Wolfe, Roland, UA002.008.069.00073 (Box 69)
  - Xu, Zhenkang, UA002.008.069.00074 (Box 69)
  - Yamarik, Steven, UA002.008.069.00075 (Box 69)
  - Yoon, Lee-Sung, UA002.008.069.00076 (Box 69)
  - Zukerman, Udi, UA002.008.069.00077 (Box 69)
  - Tenure History|Faculty Tenure and Promotion, 1947 -- 1991; UA002.008.070.00001 (Box 70)
  - Arts & Sciences Tenure and Promotion, 1963 -- 1992; UA002.008.070.00002 (Box 70)
  - Trustee ad hoc Committee on Faculty Appointments and Tenure, 1968 -- 2000; UA002.008.070.00003 (Box 70)
  - Tenure + Prom., 1994 -- 1996; UA002.008.070.00004 (Box 70)
  - Tenure Histories, 1978 -- 1996; UA002.008.070.00005 (Box 70)
  - Tenure Procedures Prof. Schools, 1989 -- 1997; UA002.008.070.00006 (Box 70)
  - Medical Tenure, 1969 -- 1980; UA002.008.070.00007 (Box 70)
  - Dental Tenure, 1969 -- 1981; UA002.008.070.00008 (Box 70)
  - Tenure History, 1970 -- 1996; UA002.008.070.00009 (Box 70)
  - Tenure Improvement, 1996; UA002.008.070.00010 (Box 70)
  - Policy on length of stay for visiting professors, 1994 -- 1997; UA002.008.070.00011 (Box 70)
  - Dental Tracks, 1994 -- 1997; UA002.008.070.00012 (Box 70)
  - Appointment titles, 1981 -- 1996; UA002.008.070.00013 (Box 70)
  - Appointments - cont. term, 1995 -- 1996; UA002.008.070.00014 (Box 70)
  - Tenure tracking, 1996; UA002.008.070.00015 (Box 70)
  - Tenure procedures- Provost office, 1973 -- 1996; UA002.008.070.00016 (Box 70)
  - Tenure wkshop, 1996; UA002.008.070.00017 (Box 70)
  - (A&S) Tenure policies and procedures, 1966 -- 1994; UA002.008.070.00018 (Box 70)
  - Tenure - medicine, 1996 -- 1997; UA002.008.070.00019 (Box 70)
  - Tuition Remission - PT, 1992 -- 1997; UA002.008.070.00020 (Box 70)
  - Trustee Bylaws, 1924 -- 1995; UA002.008.070.00021 (Box 70)
  - A+S (including LA + J, Engg, GSAS and BSOT) By laws, 1982 -- 1998; UA002.008.070.00022 (Box 70)
  - Sabbatic leaves, 1968 -- 1974; UA002.008.070.00023 (Box 70)
  - Research Prof., 1981 -- 1996; UA002.008.070.00024 (Box 70)
  - Restraining orders, 1996; UA002.008.070.00025 (Box 70)
  - New preface for bylaws, 1984; UA002.008.070.00026 (Box 70)
  - Dental bylaws, 1977 -- 1993; UA002.008.070.00027 (Box 70)
  - Fletcher bylaws, 1956; UA002.008.070.00028 (Box 70)
  - Sachler School bylaws, UA002.008.070.00029 (Box 70)
  - Special Studies bylaws, 1976 -- 1982; UA002.008.070.00030 (Box 70)
  - Nutrition faculty, 1955 -- 1996; UA002.008.070.00031 (Box 70)
  - Past tenure review, 1996; UA002.008.070.00032 (Box 70)
  - Tenure & promotion charts/April AA, 1998 -- 1999; UA002.008.070.00033 (Box 70)
  - Pathology, 1981 -- 1996; UA002.008.070.00034 (Box 70)
  - Guidelines for Full-Time Faculty Appointments, 1987; UA002.008.070.00035 (Box 70)
  - FSNSP bylaws, 2001 -- 2003; UA002.008.070.00036 (Box 70)
  - Dental contract track, 1979 -- 1994; UA002.008.070.00037 (Box 70)
  - School of Dental Medicine Faculty Handbook, 2000; UA002.008.071.00001 (Box 71)
  - School of Veterinary Medicine Faculty Handbook, 2004; UA002.008.071.00002 (Box 71)
  - PAF Logbook, 2008 -- 2009; UA002.008.071.00003 (Box 71)
  - PAF Logbook, 2009 -- 2010; UA002.008.071.00004 (Box 71)
  - Faculty Profile Book CD, 2011 -- 2012; UA002.008.071.00005 (Box 71)
  - Tufts Crisis Management Plan, 2005; UA002.008.071.00006 (Box 71)
  - Tufts University Faculty Handbook, 1970; UA002.008.071.00007 (Box 71)
  - Faculty Handbook, Health Schiences Campus [1 of 2], 1983; UA002.008.071.00008 (Box 71)
  - Faculty Handbook, Health Schiences Campus [2 of 2], 1983; UA002.008.071.00009 (Box 71)
  - Fletcher Faculty Handbook, 2001; UA002.008.071.00010 (Box 71)
  - School of Medicine Policy Letters, 1988 -- 1989; UA002.008.071.00011 (Box 71)
  - College of Special Studies: Taskforce Originals, 1995; UA002.008.071.00012 (Box 71)
  - Dissolving One Medicine [1 of 2], 2000; UA002.008.071.00013 (Box 71)
  - Dissolving One Medicine [2 of 2], 2000; UA002.008.071.00014 (Box 71)
  - Arts & Sciences Faculty Handbook, 1985; UA002.008.071.00015 (Box 71)
  - Report of the Info Technology Task Force, 1996; UA002.008.071.00016 (Box 71)
  - Health Sciences Education Buildig Program Concept and Project Criteria, 1982; UA002.008.071.00017 (Box 71)
  - Draft Friedman School Faculty Handbook, 2001; UA002.008.071.00018 (Box 71)
  - Health Sciences Boston Campus Institutional Master Plan, 1993; UA002.008.071.00019 (Box 71)
  - Amy Yee Binder 1, 2010; UA002.008.071.00020 (Box 71)
    Research Misconduct Investigation
  - Amy Yee Binder 2, 2010; UA002.008.071.00021 (Box 71)
  - Amy Yee, 2010 -- 2011; UA002.008.071.00022 (Box 71)
  - PhD in Comparative Biomedical Sciences TCSVM, 2000; UA002.008.071.00023 (Box 71)
  - MS in Comparative Biomedical Sciences TCSVM, 2003 -- 2004; UA002.008.071.00024 (Box 71)
  - MS in Conservation Medicine TCSVM, 2009; UA002.008.071.00025 (Box 71)
  - International Veterinary Medicine Certificate, 2010; UA002.008.071.00026 (Box 71)
  - DMD/MS in Dental Research, 2011; UA002.008.071.00027 (Box 71)
  - Masters in Nutrition - UAE, 2007; UA002.008.071.00028 (Box 71)
  - Certificate in Humanitarian Studies, 2001; UA002.008.071.00029 (Box 71)
  - MS in Nutrition Science and Policy - UAE, 2007; UA002.008.071.00030 (Box 71)
  - MALD/MBA: Fletcher and Groupe HEC, 1995; UA002.008.071.00031 (Box 71)
  - MIB (formerly MSCIM) Fletcher, 2006; UA002.008.071.00032 (Box 71)
  - LLM Fletcher, 2007; UA002.008.071.00033 (Box 71)
  - MALD/MAIS w/Vienna School of International Studies, 2005; UA002.008.071.00034 (Box 71)
  - GMAP, 2000; UA002.008.071.00035 (Box 71)
  - Astill, Kenneth, UA002.008.072.00001 (Box 72)
  - Bedau, Hugo, UA002.008.072.00002 (Box 72)
  - Dice, James, UA002.008.072.00003 (Box 72)
  - Donnenfeld, O. Walter, UA002.008.072.00004 (Box 72)
  - Drooker, Joshua, UA002.008.072.00005 (Box 72)
  - Gianelly, Ralph, UA002.008.072.00006 (Box 72)
  - Gibb, Thomas, UA002.008.072.00007 (Box 72)
  - Gibson, John S., UA002.008.072.00008 (Box 72)
  - Goldner, Ron, UA002.008.072.00009 (Box 72)
  - Green, Martin B., UA002.008.072.00010 (Box 72)
  - Hammerquist, Harold, UA002.008.072.00011 (Box 72)
  - Hodgson, Edward, UA002.008.072.00012 (Box 72)
  - Hughes, Walter, UA002.008.072.00013 (Box 72)
  - Kelma, Ernest, UA002.008.072.00014 (Box 72)
  - Krinsky, Norman, UA002.008.072.00015 (Box 72)
  - Krumme, David, UA002.008.072.00016 (Box 72)
  - Lawrence, Elizabeth, UA002.008.072.00017 (Box 72)
  - Levesque, Paul, UA002.008.072.00018 (Box 72)
  - Madoc-Jones, Hywel, UA002.008.072.00019 (Box 72)
  - Mahler, Donald, UA002.008.072.00020 (Box 72)
  - Marcopoulos, George, UA002.008.072.00021 (Box 72)
  - O'Leary, James, UA002.008.072.00022 (Box 72)
  - Rheinlander, Harold, UA002.008.072.00023 (Box 72)
  - Sampson, Philip, UA002.008.072.00024 (Box 72)
  - Schwartz, Bernard, UA002.008.072.00025 (Box 72)
  - Schwartz, Stanley, UA002.008.072.00026 (Box 72)
  - Schwartz, William, UA002.008.072.00027 (Box 72)
  - Seasholes, Bradbury, UA002.008.072.00028 (Box 72)
  - Stange, G. Robert, UA002.008.072.00029 (Box 72)
  - Susi, Frank, UA002.008.072.00030 (Box 72)
  - Wellington, C. Burleigh, UA002.008.072.00031 (Box 72)
  - Whitehead, Kathleen, UA002.008.072.00032 (Box 72)
  - Whittredge, Ruth, UA002.008.072.00033 (Box 72)
  - Wright, Mary, UA002.008.072.00034 (Box 72)
  - Zarker, John, UA002.008.072.00035 (Box 72)
  - Palubinskas Daly, A. Lucille, UA002.008.072.00036 (Box 72)
  - Department Chair Lists to Trustees, 1975 -- 2011; UA002.008.072.00037 (Box 72)
  - Purchasing, 1995 -- 2007; UA002.008.072.00038 (Box 72)
  - MD/MBA Historical Documents, 1990 -- 1995; UA002.008.072.00039 (Box 72)
  - MS in Health Communication, 1993 -- 2000; UA002.008.072.00040 (Box 72)
  - MS in Pain Research, Education, + Policy, 1998 -- 2006; UA002.008.072.00041 (Box 72)
  - MPH Degree Creation, 1995; UA002.008.072.00042 (Box 72)
  - Sackler Graduate Program in Genetics, 1993; UA002.008.072.00043 (Box 72)
  - Masters of Medical Science, 2011; UA002.008.072.00044 (Box 72)
  - Doctorate in Public Health, 2011; UA002.008.072.00045 (Box 72)
  - MS in Biomedical Sciences, 2006; UA002.008.072.00046 (Box 72)
  - Master of Surgical Anatomy, 2006; UA002.008.072.00047 (Box 72)
  - MS/PhD in Clinical Care Research, 1999; UA002.008.072.00048 (Box 72)
  - MA in Bioethics, 2001; UA002.008.072.00049 (Box 72)
  - MBS/MBA Combined Degree with Brandeis, 2010; UA002.008.072.00050 (Box 72)
  - Fletcher MA/TUSM MD 2006 (formerly MD/MALD program), UA002.008.072.00051 (Box 72)
  - Fletcher MA/Tufts BA, 1973; UA002.008.072.00052 (Box 72)
  - Guidelines for New Degree Proposals, 1996 -- 2009; UA002.008.072.00053 (Box 72)
  - MS in Nutrition and MPH, 1997; UA002.008.072.00054 (Box 72)
  - BS/BA and MPH, 1999; UA002.008.072.00055 (Box 72)
  - BS in Engineering and MD, 1996; UA002.008.072.00056 (Box 72)
  - BS + MS in Engineering and DMD, 1998; UA002.008.072.00057 (Box 72)
  - BA/BS + DMD, 1998; UA002.008.072.00058 (Box 72)
  - BS in Engineering and MALD, 1998; UA002.008.072.00059 (Box 72)
  - Miscellaneous Combined Degree Materials, 1982 -- 2003; UA002.008.072.00060 (Box 72)
  - Confidential Documents, 2008 -- 2011; UA002.008.072.00061 (Box 72)
  - Confidential Letter re: YEE, 2010 -- 2011; UA002.008.072.00062 (Box 72)
- Committee files and annual reports, 1963 -- 2003; UA002.009; 0.55 Linear Feet
  This series consists of annual reports and related correspondence by several standing and ad hoc committees to the Office of the Provost. Reports generally are informal compilations by individual committees used to produce the annual reports by the Provost to the University President.
  Original folder titles only read "Annual reports." This title proved to be misleading as it did not differentiate these records from files in the series "Annual reports" and because folders, in fact, also contain committee related correspondence. We therefore inserted "Committee files" in the title. Individual committee reports may also be found in the series "Subject Files" (boxes 1-21).
  For reports issued by the Office of the Provost to the President as well as reports from Deans and Chairs to the Provost, see "Annual Reports." For reports issued by departments to the Office of the Provost, see "Department Records."
  This series is arranged chronologically by academic year.
  - Committee files and annual reports, 1968 -- 1970; UA002.009.047.00001 (Box 47)
  - Committee files and annual reports, 1970 -- 1971; UA002.009.047.00002 (Box 47)
  - Committee files and annual reports, 1971 -- 1972; UA002.009.047.00003 (Box 47)
  - Committee files and annual reports, 1972 -- 1973; UA002.009.047.00004 (Box 47)
  - Committee files and annual reports, 1973 -- 1974; UA002.009.047.00005 (Box 47)
  - Committee files and annual reports, 1974 -- 1975; UA002.009.047.00006 (Box 47)
  - Committee files and annual reports, 1975 -- 1976; UA002.009.047.00007 (Box 47)
  - Committee files and annual reports, 1976 -- 1977; UA002.009.047.00008 (Box 47)
  - Committee files and annual reports, 1977 -- 1978; UA002.009.047.00009 (Box 47)
  - Committee files and annual reports, 1978 -- 1979; UA002.009.047.00010 (Box 47)
  - Committee files and annual reports, 1979 -- 1980; UA002.009.047.00011 (Box 47)
  - Committee files and annual reports, 1980 -- 1981; UA002.009.047.00012 (Box 47)
  - Committee files and annual reports, 1981 -- 1982; UA002.009.047.00013 (Box 47)
  - Committee files and annual reports, 1982 -- 1983; UA002.009.047.00014 (Box 47)
  - Committee files and annual reports, 1 of 2, 1983 -- 1984; UA002.009.047.00015 (Box 47)
  - Committee files and annual reports, 2 of 2, 1983 -- 1984; UA002.009.047.00016 (Box 47)
  - Committee files and annual reports, 1984 -- 1985; UA002.009.047.00017 (Box 47)
  - Committee files and annual reports, 1985 -- 1986; UA002.009.047.00018 (Box 47)
  - Committee files and annual reports, 1986 -- 1987; UA002.009.047.00019 (Box 47)
  - Committee files and annual reports, 1987 -- 1988; UA002.009.047.00020 (Box 47)
  - [Patents, Licenses and Copyright 1 of 3], 1985 -- 1997; UA002.009.059.00001 (Box 59)
  - [Patents, Licenses and Copyright 2 of 3], 1982 -- 1985; UA002.009.059.00002 (Box 59)
  - [Patents, Licenses and Copyright 3 of 3], 1980 -- 1982; UA002.009.059.00003 (Box 59)
  - Post-retirement Health Benefits Committee, Spring 1992 [1 of 2], 1992 -- 1993; UA002.009.059.00004 (Box 59)
  - Post-retirement Health Benefits Committee, Spring 1992 [2 of 2], UA002.009.059.00005 (Box 59)
  - Accreditation 1992 - Organization and Governance Com., 1986 -- 1991; UA002.009.059.00006 (Box 59)
  - Reaccreditation Organization and Committee 1992 - Working papers [1 of 2], UA002.009.059.00007 (Box 59)
  - Reaccreditation Organization and Committee 1992 - Working papers [2 of 2], UA002.009.059.00008 (Box 59)
  - Report of the Committee on Undergraduate Education, 1975; UA002.009.059.00009 (Box 59)
  - Tuition Benefits Committee 91-92 [1 of 2], 1978 -- 1992; UA002.009.059.00010 (Box 59)
  - Tuition Benefits Committee 91-92 [2 of 2], 1991; UA002.009.059.00011 (Box 59)
  - Tuition Task Force and policies, 1978 -- 1982; UA002.009.059.00012 (Box 59)
  - Tuition Task Force and policies, 1983 -- 1986; UA002.009.059.00013 (Box 59)
  - Tuition Remission Benefits Committee, 1987; UA002.009.059.00014 (Box 59)
  - History of Tuition Benefits [1 of 2], 1963 -- 1989; UA002.009.059.00015 (Box 59)
  - History of Tuition Benefits [2 of 2], 1963 -- 1989; UA002.009.059.00016 (Box 59)
  - Tuition Gratuities and Grants in Aid, 1965 -- 1976; UA002.009.059.00017 (Box 59)
  - Benefits Advisory Committee, 1993; UA002.009.060.00014 (Box UA002 Shared 1)
  - Committee on Social Fraternity and Sorority Life [1 of 2], 1988 -- 1994; UA002.009.060.00015 (Box UA002 Shared 1)
  - Committee on Social Fraternity and Sorority Life [2 of 2], 1988; UA002.009.060.00016 (Box UA002 Shared 1)
  - Committee on Fraternities and Sororities, 1993; UA002.009.060.00017 (Box UA002 Shared 1)
  - Dormitory and Building Plaque Statements by William D. Hersey, 2002 -- 2003; UA002.009.060.00018 (Box UA002 Shared 1)